Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part One
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Files, 1710-1955; 21.07; (65 boxes)
  - Planché, J. R. (James Robinson), 1796- 1880, 1871-72, undated (Box 47, Folder 1705)
  - Playfair, Arthur Wyndham, 1869-1918, 1895, undated (Box 47, Folder 1706)
  - Playfair, Lyon Playfair, Baron, 1818- 1898, 1878, undated (Box 47, Folder 1707)
  - Plimsoll, Samuel, 1824-1898, 1875-76, undated (Box 47, Folder 1708)
  - Plunkett Greene, Henry, 1865-1936, 1899 (Box 47, Folder 1709)
  - Plymtree, Devons, undated (Box 47, Folder 1710)
  - Pollock, Jonathan Frederick, Sir, Bart., 1783-1870, 1838-66, undated (Box 47, Folder 1711)
  - Pollock, Walter Herries, 1850-1926, 1865-92 (Box 47, Folder 1712)
  - Polworth, L., 1859 (Box 47, Folder 1713)
  - Ponsonby, Henry Frederick, Sir, 1825- 1895, 1870-94, undated (Box 47, Folder 1714)
  - Ponsonby-Fane, Spencer Cecil Brabazon, Sir, 1824-1915, 1909, undated (Box 47, Folder 1715)
  - Poole, Elizabeth, 1820-1906, 1879 (Box 47, Folder 1716)
  - Poole, Reginald Lane, 1857-1939, 1909 (Box 47, Folder 1717)
  - Poole, Reginald Stuart, 1832-1895, 1881-87 (Box 47, Folder 1718)
  - Porter, Robert Ker, Sir, 1777-1842, 1841 (Box 48, Folder 1719)
  - Portland, William Henry Cavendish Scott Bentinck, Duke of, 1768-1854, 1836-50, undated (Box 48, Folder 1720)
  - Portland, William John Cavendish- Scott-Bentinck, Duke of, 1800-1879, 1837-67, undated (Box 48, Folder 1721)
  - Portman, Edward Berkeley Portman, Viscount, 1799-1888, 1829-57, undated (Box 48, Folder 1722)
  - Portsman, Isaac Newton Wallop, Earl, 1825-1891, 1862-1905, undated (Box 48, Folder 1723)
  - Pott, Laslett, 1837-1898, 1898, undated (Box 48, Folder 1724)
  - Potter, Philip Cipriani Hambly, 1792- 1871, 1836 (Box 48, Folder 1725)
  - Potter, Cora Urquhart, 1859-1936, undated (Box 48, Folder 1726)
  - Potter, Thomas Bayley, 1817-1898, 1883 (Box 48, Folder 1727)
  - Pottinger, Henry, Sir, 1789-1856, 1845-46 (Box 48, Folder 1728)
  - Powell, F. York (Frederick York), 1850-1904, 1890-1900, undated (Box 48, Folder 1729)
  - Power, Nelly, undated (Box 48, Folder 1730)
  - Powers, Hiram, 1805-1873, undated (Box 48, Folder 1731)
  - Poynter, Edward John, Sir, Bart., 1836-1919, 1867-1912, undated (Box 48, Folder 1732)
  - Pratt, Hodgson, 1824-1907, 1878 (Box 48, Folder 1733)
  - Pratt, John Henry, d. 1871, 1856 (Box 48, Folder 1734)
  - Pratten, Catherina Josepha (Pelzer), d. 1895, 1882 (Box 48, Folder 1735)
  - Prince, J.W., 1887 (Box 48, Folder 1736)
  - Prinsep, Valentine Cameron, 1838-1904, 1890-98 (Box 48, Folder 1737)
  - Probyn, Dighton Macnaghten, Sir, 1833- 1924, 1879-1916, undated (Box 48, Folder 1738)
  - Prothero, George, undated (Box 48, Folder 1739)
  - Prout, Ebenezer, 1835-1909, 1878 (Box 48, Folder 1740)
  - Prout, Samuel, 1783-1852, undated (Box 48, Folder 1741)
  - Pugin, Augustus Welby Northmore, 1812- 1852, 1841, undated (Box 48, Folder 1742)
  - Pyne, Louisa Fanny, 1828-1904, 1862, undated (Box 48, Folder 1743)
  - Quain, Richard, Sir, 1816-1898, 1862, undated (Box 48, Folder 1744)
  - Quilter, William Cuthbert, Sir, Bart., 1814-1911, 1897 (Box 48, Folder 1745)
  - Quin, Michael J. (Michael Joseph), 1796-1843, 1842 (Box 48, Folder 1746)
  - Radcliffe, John, undated (Box 48, Folder 1747)
  - Radcliffe, Pauline Rita, 1888 (Box 48, Folder 1748)
  - Radstock, Granville Augustus William Waldegrave, Baron, 1833-1913, undated (Box 48, Folder 1749)
  - Radziwill, Catherine, Princess, 1858- 1941, undated (Box 48, Folder 1750)
  - Raglan, Richard Henry FitzRoy Somerset, Baron, 1817-1884, 1864 (Box 49, Folder 1751)
  - Rainforth, Elizabeth, 1814-1877, undated (Box 49, Folder 1752)
  - Ramsay, William, 1852-1916, undated (Box 49, Folder 1753)
  - Randall, Harry, 1860-1932, undated (Box 49, Folder 1754)
  - Randegger, Alberto, 1832-1911, 1880-1901, undated (Box 49, Folder 1755)
  - Ranken, J., d. 1845, 1845-75 (Box 49, Folder 1756)
  - Rankley, Alfred, 1819-1872, 1863-64 (Box 49, Folder 1757)
  - Ransford, Edward, 1805-1876, 1862 (Box 49, Folder 1758)
  - Rathbone, W.G., 1893 (Box 49, Folder 1759)
  - Ravensworth, Henry George Liddell, Earl, 1821-1903, 1854-87, undated (Box 49, Folder 1760)
  - Ravensworth, Henry Thomas Liddell, Earl, 1797-1878, 1834-56, undated (Box 49, Folder 1761)
  - Rawlinson, 1812-1902, 1871 (Box 49, Folder 1762)
  - Rawson, Rawson William, Sir, 1812-1899, 1894-97 (Box 49, Folder 1763)
  - Rayne, Leonard, 1901 (Box 49, Folder 1764)
  - Reach, Angus B. (Angus Bethune), 1821- 1856, undated (Box 49, Folder 1765)
  - Redesdale, John Thomas Freeman- Mitford, Earl, 1805-1886, 1872 (Box 49, Folder 1766)
  - Redgrave, Richard, 1804-1888, 1842-73, undated (Box 49, Folder 1767)
  - Redhead, Richard, 1820-1901, 1881, undated (Box 49, Folder 1768)
  - Reece, Robert, 1838-1891, 1871-91, undated (Box 49, Folder 1769)
  - Reed, Alfred German, 1847-1895, 1881, undated (Box 49, Folder 1770)
  - Reed, Edward Tennyson, 1860-1933, 1884-1903, undated (Box 49, Folder 1771)
  - Reed, Thomas German, 1817-1888, 1863-80 (Box 49, Folder 1772)
  - Reeves, Sims, 1818-1900, 1850-97, undated (Box 49, Folder 1773)
  - Regondi, Giulio, 1822-1872, 1872, undated (Box 49, Folder 1774)
  - Rennell, James Rennell Rodd, Baron, 1858-1941, undated (Box 49, Folder 1775)
  - Reuter, L., undated (Box 49, Folder 1776)
  - Reuter, Paul Julius, Baron de, 1821- 1899, undated (Box 49, Folder 1777)
  - Reventlow, Countess, 1863-66 (Box 49, Folder 1778)
  - Reynolds, Frederick, 1764-1841, undated (Box 49, Folder 1779)
  - Reynolds, George W.M. (George William MacArthur), 1814-1879, 1856 (Box 49, Folder 1780)
  - Rhodes, Helen Guy, 1858-1936, undated (Box 49, Folder 1781)
  - Ribbesdale, Thomas Lister, Baron, 1854-1925, 1899-1909 (Box 49, Folder 1782)
  - Richard, Henry, 1812-1888, 1872 (Box 49, Folder 1783)
  - Richards, Brinley, 1819-1885, 1861-79 (Box 49, Folder 1784)
  - Richards, Cicely, undated (Box 49, Folder 1785)
  - Richards, James Brinsley, 1846-1892, 1886, undated (Box 49, Folder 1786)
  - Richardson, Frank, undated (Box 49, Folder 1787)
  - Richardson, Thomas Miles, 1813-1890, 1865-72 (Box 49, Folder 1788)
  - Richardson, W., fl. 1842-1877, 1879 (Box 49, Folder 1789)
  - Richmond, George, 1809-1896, 1850-90, undated (Box 49, Folder 1790)
  - Richmond, William Blake, Sir, 1843- 1921, 1880-1900, undated (Box 49, Folder 1791)
  - Richmond and Gordon, Charles Henry Gordon-Lennox, Duke of, 1818-1903, 1857-1902 (Box 49, Folder 1792)
  - Richter, Davis, 1889 (Box 49, Folder 1793)
  - Richter, Hans, 1843-1916, 1884 (Box 49, Folder 1794)
  - Ricks, James, fl. 1868-1885, 1885-93 (Box 49, Folder 1795)
  - Ridley, Matthew White, Viscount, 1842- 1904, 1876-89, undated (Box 50, Folder 1796)
  - Rigby, Vernon, b. 1840, 1874, undated (Box 50, Folder 1797)
  - Righton, Thomas Edward Corrie Burns, d. 1899, undated (Box 50, Folder 1798)
  - Rimbault, Edward F. (Edward Francis), 1816-1876, 1869, undated (Box 50, Folder 1799)
  - Rimer, Louisa Serena, fl. 1855-1875, 1856 (Box 50, Folder 1800)
  - Rimer, William, fl. 1845-1885, 1851 (Box 50, Folder 1801)
  - Rimington, Alexander W. (Alexander Wallace), 1854-1918, undated (Box 50, Folder 1802)
  - Ripon, Frederick Oliver Robinson, Marquess of, 1852-1923, 1894-1915 (Box 50, Folder 1803)
  - Ripon, George Frederick Samuel Robinson, Marquess of, 1827-1909, 1860-1901, undated (Box 50, Folder 1804)
  - Rippingille, Edward Villiers, 1798?- 1859, undated (Box 50, Folder 1805)
  - Ristori, Adelaide, 1822-1906, 1859, undated (Box 50, Folder 1806)
  - Ritchie, Anne Thackeray, 1837-1919, undated (Box 50, Folder 1807)
  - Ritchie, J. Ewing (James Ewing), 1820- 1898, 1895, undated (Box 50, Folder 1808)
  - Rivers, Horace Pitt-Rivers, Baron, 1814-1880, 1869, undated (Box 50, Folder 1809)
  - Rivers, Kate, 1867 (Box 50, Folder 1810)
  - Rives, Amélie, 1863-1945, 1896 (Box 50, Folder 1811)
  - Rivett-Carnac, Lady, d. 1859, undated (Box 50, Folder 1812)
  - Rivière, Briton, 1840-1920, 1873-1900, undated (Box 50, Folder 1813)
  - Riviere, Henry Parsons, 1811-1888, 1880-86 (Box 50, Folder 1814)
  - Riviere, Hugh Godwin, 1869-1956, 1907 (Box 50, Folder 1815)
  - Robert, John Varley, 1841-1920, 1899 (Box 50, Folder 1816)
  - Roberts, Arthur, 1852-1933, 1896-1904, undated (Box 50, Folder 1817)
  - Roberts, David, 1796-1864, 1846-64, undated (Box 50, Folder 1818)
  - Roberts, Emma, 1794?-1840, 1832 (Box 50, Folder 1819)
  - Roberts, Morley, 1857-1942, 1896, undated (Box 50, Folder 1820)
  - Robertson, Alexander, 1815-1891, 1851 (Box 50, Folder 1821)
  - Robertson, Dion, 1887-89 (Box 50, Folder 1822)
  - Robertson, Ian Forbes, b. 1858, undated (Box 50, Folder 1823)
  - Robins, Arthur, 1834-1899 (Box 50, Folder 1824)
  - Robins, George Henry, 1778-1847, 1843, undated (Box 50, Folder 1825)
  - Robinson, A. Mary F. (Agnes Mary Frances), 1857-1944, undated (Box 50, Folder 1826)
  - Robinson, E. Kay (Edward Kay), 1857- 1928, 1905 (Box 50, Folder 1827)
  - Robinson, Frida, 1899 (Box 50, Folder 1828)
  - Robinson, J., father of Emma Robinson, 1814-1890, undated (Box 50, Folder 1829)
  - Robinson, J.C. (John Charles), Sir, 1824-1913, 1888, undated (Box 50, Folder 1830)
  - Robinson, John R. (John Richard), Sir, 1828-1903, 1892-99, undated (Box 50, Folder 1831)
  - Rochefort, Henri, 1831-1913, 1893-96, undated (Box 50, Folder 1832)
  - Roden, William Thomas, 1817-1892, 1839 (Box 51, Folder 1833)
  - Rodney, Paul, undated (Box 51, Folder 1834)
  - Roe, Bassett, b. 1860, undated (Box 51, Folder 1835)
  - Roebuck, John Arthur, 1801-1879, 1832-77, undated (Box 51, Folder 1836)
  - Roeckel, Edward, 1816-1899, 1866 (Box 51, Folder 1837)
  - Roeckel, Jane, 1838-1908, 1884 (Box 51, Folder 1838)
  - Roeckel, Joseph Leopold, 1838-1908, 1890, undated (Box 51, Folder 1839)
  - Roffe, W. J., fl. 1845-1889, 1856 (Box 51, Folder 1840)
  - Rogers, John R., 1886, undated (Box 51, Folder 1841)
  - Rogers, William Harry, 1848-61, undated (Box 51, Folder 1842)
  - Roget, Peter Mark, 1777-1869, 1864 (Box 51, Folder 1843)
  - Rolle of Stevenstone, John Rolle, Baron, 1750-1842, 1791-1833, undated (Box 51, Folder 1844)
  - Romer, Robert, 1843 (Box 51, Folder 1845)
  - Romilly, Charles, 1808-1887, 1835 (Box 51, Folder 1846)
  - Romilly, Frederick, 1810-1887, 1852 (Box 51, Folder 1847)
  - Romilly, John Romilly, Baron, 1802- 1874, 1851-68, undated (Box 51, Folder 1848)
  - Romilly, Samuel, Sir, 1757-1818, 1806-18, undated (Box 51, Folder 1849)
  - Romney, Charles Marsham, Earl, 1808- 1874, 1843-61 (Box 51, Folder 1850)
  - Romney, James, 1786-1863, undated (Box 51, Folder 1851)
  - Roninger, M. J., undated (Box 51, Folder 1852)
  - Rooke, Irene, undated (Box 51, Folder 1853)
  - Ropes, Arthur Reed, 1859-1933, 1899 (Box 51, Folder 1854)
  - Rorke, Kate, b. 1866, undated (Box 51, Folder 1855)
  - Rosa, Carl August Nicholas, 1842-1889, 1881 (Box 51, Folder 1856)
  - Rosa, Euphrosyne (Parepa), 1836-1874, undated (Box 51, Folder 1857)
  - Rose, Edward, 1849-1904, 1888-89 (Box 51, Folder 1858)
  - Rose, Philip Frederick, Sir, Bart., 1843-1919, 1894 (Box 51, Folder 1859)
  - Rose, William, Sir, Bart., 1846-1902, 1875 (Box 51, Folder 1860)
  - Rosebery, Archibald Philip Primrose, Earl of, 1847-1929, 1876-1920, undated (Box 51, Folder 1861)
  - Ross, Adrian, 1859-1933
    See: Ropes, Arthur Reed, 1859-1933, box 51, folder 1854
  - Ross, Charles, 1872-77, undated (Box 51, Folder 1862)
  - Rosse, Wiliam Parsons, Earl of, 1800- 1867, 1859, undated (Box 51, Folder 1863)
  - Rosslyn, James Francis Harry St. Claire-Erskine, Earl of, 1869-1929, 1901 (Box 51, Folder 1864)
  - Rothschild, Alfred Charles de, 1842- 1918, 1893-99, undated (Box 51, Folder 1865)
  - Rothschild, Anthony de, Sir, Bart., 1810-1876, 1859 (Box 51, Folder 1866)
  - Rothschild, Arthur de, 1851-1903, 1869 (Box 51, Folder 1867)
  - Rothschild, Emma Louisa de Rothschild, 1844-1935, 1885 (Box 51, Folder 1868)
  - Rothschild, Ferdinand, Baron, 1839-1898, 1866-95, undated (Box 51, Folder 1869)
  - Rothschild, Juliana (Cohen), 1831-1877, undated (Box 51, Folder 1870)
  - Rothschild, Leopold de, 1845-1917, 1871-1914, undated (Box 51, Folder 1871)
  - Rothschild, Lionel Nathan de, Baron, 1808-1879, 1864 (Box 51, Folder 1872)
  - Rothschild, Lionel Walter Rothschild, Baron, 1868-1937, 1916-26 (Box 51, Folder 1873)
  - Rothschild, Louisa Montefiore, Lady de, 1821-1910, 1862 (Box 51, Folder 1874)
  - Rothschild, Nathan Mayer, Baron, 1840- 1915, 1886-1921 (Box 51, Folder 1875)
  - Rothschild, Nathan Mayer, 1777-1836, undated (Box 51, Folder 1876)
  - Rougemont, Francis F., 1840-63, undated (Box 52, Folder 1877)
  - Rousby, Clara Marion Jessie, 1852?- 1879, undated (Box 52, Folder 1878)
  - Routledge, Edmund, 1843-1899, 1889 (Box 52, Folder 1879)
  - Routledge, George, 1812-1888, 1886 (Box 52, Folder 1880)
  - Rowton, Montagu William Lowry-Corry, Baron, 1838-1903, 1860-99, undated (Box 52, Folder 1881)
  - Roxburghe, Anne Emily (Spencer- Churchill) Innes-Ker, Duchess of, 1854-1923, 1873, undated (Box 52, Folder 1882)
  - Roxburghe, James Henry Robert Innes- Ker, Duke of, 1839-1892, undated (Box 52, Folder 1883)
  - Roxburghe, Susanna Stephenia (Dalbiac) Innes-Ker, Duchess of, 1814-1895, 1840-90, undated (Box 52, Folder 1884)
  - Roxby, Robert, 1809?-1866, undated (Box 52, Folder 1885)
  - Roze, Marie Hippolyte, b. 1846, 1887 (Box 52, Folder 1886)
  - Rubini, Giovanni Battista, 1795-1854, 1841-60, undated (Box 52, Folder 1887)
  - Rudersdorf, Ermine, 1822-1882, 1860 (Box 52, Folder 1888)
  - Russell, Arthur John Edward, 1825-1892, 1850-57, undated (Box 52, Folder 1889)
  - Russell, Charles James Fox, 1807-1894, 1872, undated (Box 52, Folder 1890)
  - Russell, Dora, undated (Box 52, Folder 1891)
  - Russell, Frances Anna Maria, Lady, Countess, d. 1898, 1896, undated (Box 52, Folder 1892)
  - Russell, Francis Albert Rollo, 1849- 1914, 1878-86 (Box 52, Folder 1893)
  - Russell, George, Sir, Bart., 1828-1898, 1865 (Box 52, Folder 1894)
  - Russell, George William Erskine, 1853- 1919, 1882-1915 (Box 52, Folder 1895)
  - Russell, Henry, 1812-1900, 1857, undated (Box 52, Folder 1896)
  - Russell, James, 1852 (Box 52, Folder 1897)
  - Russell, John Russell, Earl, 1792-1878, 1839-65 (Box 52, Folder 1898)
  - Russell, Samuel Thomas, 1769?-1845, undated (Box 52, Folder 1899)
  - Rutland, Charles Cecil John, Duke of, 1815-1888, 1840-88, undated (Box 52, Folder 1900)
  - Rutland, John Henry Manners, Duke of, 1778-1857, 1827-54 (Box 52, Folder 1901)
  - Rutland, John James Robert Manners, Duke of, 1818-1906, 1845-83, undated (Box 52, Folder 1902)
  - Rye, William Brenchley, 1818-1901, 1867 (Box 52, Folder 1903)
  - Ryland, Henry, 1856-1924, 1897, undated (Box 52, Folder 1904)
  - Sadler, Walter Dendy, 1854-1923, 1886-94, undated (Box 52, Folder 1905-1906)
  - Sainsbury, William Noel, 1825-1895, 1858 (Box 52, Folder 1907)
  - St-Albins, A., 1845 (Box 52, Folder 1908)
  - St. Aldwyn, Michael Edward Hicks- Beach, Earl, 1837-1916, 1874-1907, undated (Box 52, Folder 1909)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, 1848-1907, undated (Box 52, Folder 1910)
  - St. George, Julia, undated (Box 52, Folder 1911)
  - St. Helier, Francis Henry Jeune, Baron, 1843-1905, 1870-1901, undated (Box 53, Folder 1912)
  - St. John, Florence, 1854-1912, 1901 (Box 53, Folder 1913)
  - Saint Vincent, Edward Jervis Jervis, Viscount, 1767-1859, 1838 (Box 53, Folder 1914)
  - Sainton, Prosper Philippe Catherine, 1813-1890, 1889 (Box 53, Folder 1915)
  - Sainton-Dolby, Charlotte H., 1821-1885, 1868-83, undated (Box 53, Folder 1916)
  - Sale, J. B. (John Bernard), 1776-1856, 1838 (Box 53, Folder 1917)
  - Salisbury, Georgiana Caroline (Alderson) Gascoyne-Cecil, Marchioness of, d. 1899, undated (Box 53, Folder 1918)
  - Salisbury, James Brownlow William Gascoyne-Cecil, Marquess of, 1791-1868, 1838-68 (Box 53, Folder 1919)
  - Salisbury, James Edward Hubert Gascoyne-Cecil, Marquess of, 1861-1947, 1885-1912 (Box 53, Folder 1920)
  - Salisbury, Robert Cecil, Marquess of, 1830-1903, 1867-94 (Box 53, Folder 1921)
  - Salmon, Nowell, Sir, 1835-1912, 1900 (Box 53, Folder 1922)
  - Salting, George, 1835-1909, undated (Box 53, Folder 1923)
  - Salvini, Tommaso, 1829-1916, 1884-1908, undated (Box 53, Folder 1924)
  - Sambourne, Edwin Linley, 1844-1910, 1883-1906 (Box 53, Folder 1925)
  - Sandhurst, William Mansfield, Viscount, 1855-1921, 1881-1914, undated (Box 53, Folder 1926)
  - Sandys, Frederick, 1829-1904, 1862, undated (Box 53, Folder 1927)
  - Sanford, John Langton, 1824-1877, 1871 (Box 53, Folder 1928)
  - Sant, J. W., undated (Box 53, Folder 1929)
  - Sant, James, 1820-1916, 1869-84, undated (Box 53, Folder 1930)
  - Santley, Charles, Sir, 1834-1922, 1870-1913, undated (Box 53, Folder 1931)
  - Santley, Kate, 1888, undated (Box 53, Folder 1932)
  - Saunders, Edwin, Sir, 1814-1901, 1894 (Box 53, Folder 1933)
  - Saville-Clarke, Clara, undated (Box 53, Folder 1934)
  - Scannell, Edith, fl. 1870-1893, undated (Box 54, Folder 1935)
  - Scarbrough, Frederica Mary Adeliza (Drummond), Countess of, 1826-1907, undated (Box 54, Folder 1936)
  - Scarborough, Eng., "Report on Levels for Water to Scarborough", undated (Box 54, Folder 1937)
  - Scarsdale, Alfred Nathaniel Holden Curzon, Baron, 1831-1916, 1890-1900, undated (Box 54, Folder 1938)
  - Scharf, George, Sir, 1820-1895, 1856-91 (Box 54, Folder 1939)
  - Scharlieb, Mary Ann Dacomb (Bird), 1845-1930, 1898 (Box 54, Folder 1940)
  - Schmalz, Herbert, fl. 1879-1893, 1895-1905, undated (Box 54, Folder 1941)
  - Sclater, Philip Lutley, 1829-1913, 1863 (Box 54, Folder 1942)
  - Scott, Benjamin, 1814-1892, 1863 (Box 54, Folder 1943)
  - Scott, Clement, 1841-1904, 1880-1902 (Box 54, Folder 1944)
  - Scott, George Gilbert, Sir, 1811-1878, 1878, undated (Box 54, Folder 1945)
  - Scott-Gatty, Alfred, 1847-1918, 1871 (Box 54, Folder 1946)
  - Scott-Siddons, Mary, 1843-1896, 1874-75, undated (Box 54, Folder 1947)
  - Seckendorff, Theodore von, Count, d. 1910?, 1889-90 (Box 54, Folder 1948)
  - Seddon, Thomas, 1821-1856 (Box 54, Folder 1949)
  - Sedger, Horace, 1894 (Box 54, Folder 1950)
  - Selborne, Roundell Palmer, Earl of, 1812-1895, 1849-95, undated (Box 54, Folder 1951)
  - Selborne, William Waldegrave Palmer, Earl of, 1859-1942, 1892 (Box 54, Folder 1952)
  - Selby, William Court Gully, Viscount, 1835-1909, 1895-96, undated (Box 54, Folder 1953)
  - Senior, William, 1839?-1920, 1901 (Box 54, Folder 1954)
  - Senties, Thomas, fl. 1852-1858, undated (Box 54, Folder 1955)
  - Serles, Thomas James, 1839 (Box 54, Folder 1956)
  - Setchel, Sarah, 1803-1894, 1857 (Box 54, Folder 1957)
  - Seymour, George Hamilton, Sir, 1797- 1880, 1857-58, undated (Box 54, Folder 1958)
  - Shadwell, Lancelot, Sir, 1779-1850, 1844 (Box 54, Folder 1959)
  - Shaftesbury, Anthony Ashley Cooper, Earl of, 1801-1885, 1844-85, undated (Box 54, Folder 1960)
  - Shaftesbury, Anthony Ashley-Cooper, Earl of, 1869-1961, undated (Box 54, Folder 1961)
  - Sharpe, C.W., fl. 1858-1883, 1850 (Box 54, Folder 1962)
  - Shaw, John Byam, 1872-1919, 1898, undated (Box 54, Folder 1963)
  - Shaw, Richard Norman, 1831-1912, 1899, undated (Box 54, Folder 1964)
  - Shaw-Lefevre, Charles, 1794-1888, 1882 (Box 54, Folder 1965)
  - Shaw-Lefevre, John George, Sir, 1797- 1879, 1837-67, undated (Box 54, Folder 1966)
  - Shaw-Stewart, Lady, undated (Box 54, Folder 1967)
  - Shee, Martin Archer, 1769-1850, undated (Box 54, Folder 1968)
  - Sheepshanks, John, 1787-1863, 1857, undated (Box 54, Folder 1969)
  - Sheffield, Henry North Holroyd, Earl of, 1832-1909, 1857 (Box 54, Folder 1970)
  - Shepperson, Claude Allin, 1867-1921, 1898-1906, undated (Box 54, Folder 1971)
  - Sherbrooke, Robert Lowe, Viscount, 1811-1892, 1853-82, undated (Box 54, Folder 1972)
  - Shirley, Walter Shirley, 1851-1888, 1887 (Box 54, Folder 1973)
  - Shirreff, Jane, 1811-1883, undated (Box 54, Folder 1974)
  - Shore, J.G., 1880 (Box 54, Folder 1975)
  - Shorter, Clement King, 1857-1926, 1914 (Box 54, Folder 1976)
  - Sichel, Walter Sydney, 1855-1933, 1912-29, undated (Box 55, Folder 1977)
  - Sidney, Herbert, 1810-1864, undated (Box 55, Folder 1978)
  - Sidgwick, Arthur, 1840-1920, 1898-1912 (Box 55, Folder 1979)
  - Simon, John, Sir, 1818-1897, 1852, undated (Box 55, Folder 1980)
  - Simonds, George, fl. 1859-1870, 1886 (Box 55, Folder 1981)
  - Simonett, Cavaliere Attilo, 1892 (Box 55, Folder 1982)
  - Simpkinson, John Augustus Francis, Sir, 1781-1851, undated (Box 55, Folder 1983)
  - Simpson, Ernest A., undated (Box 55, Folder 1984)
  - Simpson, John, 1782-1847, 1839 (Box 55, Folder 1985)
  - Simpson, John Palgrave, 1807-1887, 1855-83, undated (Box 55, Folder 1986)
  - Simpson, W., 1881 (Box 55, Folder 1987)
  - Simpson, William, 1823-1899, 1872-90, undated (Box 55, Folder 1988)
  - Sims, E. Gordon, 1884 (Box 55, Folder 1989)
  - Sims, Henrietta, 1861 (Box 55, Folder 1990)
  - Sinclair, William Macdonald, 1850-1917, 1895-1909, undated (Box 55, Folder 1991)
  - Skerrett, M., undated (Box 55, Folder 1992)
  - Slous, A.R., undated (Box 55, Folder 1993)
  - Smallfield, Frederick, 1829-1915, 1859-79 (Box 55, Folder 1994)
  - Smetham, James, 1821-1889, 1875 (Box 55, Folder 1995)
  - Smiles, Samuel, 1812-1904, undated (Box 55, Folder 1996)
  - Smirke, Sydney, 1798-1877, undated (Box 55, Folder 1997)
  - Smith, Albert, 1816-1860, undated (Box 55, Folder 1998)
  - Smith, Charles John, 1803-1838, 1855 (Box 55, Folder 1999)
  - Smith, Charles Roach, 1807-1890, 1848-56, undated (Box 55, Folder 2000)
  - Smith, Clement, 1845-1921, 1902 (Box 55, Folder 2001)
  - Smith, E. Talbot (1804-1877), 1873 (Box 55, Folder 2002)
  - Smith, George, 1824-1901, 1872-95 (Box 55, Folder 2003)
  - Smith, George, 1829-1901, 1876 (Box 55, Folder 2004)
  - Smith, James Edward, Sir, 1759-1828, undated (Box 55, Folder 2005)
  - Smith, William, 1808-1876, 1847 (Box 55, Folder 2006)
  - Smith, William Henry, 1825-1891, 1873-91, undated (Box 55, Folder 2007)
  - Smith, William J., fl. 1837-1855, undated (Box 55, Folder 2008)
  - Smith, William, Sir, 1813-1893, 1876-86 (Box 55, Folder 2009)
  - Smithies, T. B., 1871 (Box 55, Folder 2010)
  - Smyth, Lady, undated (Box 55, Folder 2011)
  - Soane, John, Sir, 1753-1837, undated (Box 55, Folder 2012)
  - Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, 1840 (Box 55, Folder 2013)
  - Soden, John E., fl. 1861-1887, undated (Box 55, Folder 2014)
  - Soldene, Emily, c. 1845-1912, 1906 (Box 55, Folder 2015)
  - Solly, Samuel R., 1858 (Box 55, Folder 2016)
  - Solomon, Abraham, 1823-1862, undated (Box 55, Folder 2017)
  - Solomon, Solomon J. (Solomon Joseph), 1860-1927, 1881-1902, undated (Box 55, Folder 2018)
  - Somerset, Edward Adolphus Seymour, Duke of, 1804-1885, 1851-76, undated (Box 55, Folder 2019)
  - Somerset, Jane Georgiana (Sheridan) Seymour, Duchess of, 1809-1884, 1842-87, undated (Box 55, Folder 2020)
  - Sondes, George John Monson, Baron, 1794-1874, 1839, undated (Box 56, Folder 2021)
  - Soper, John Downs, 1837 (Box 56, Folder 2022)
  - Sothern, Edward Askew, 1826-1881, 1875, undated (Box 56, Folder 2023)
  - Soutar, Robert, 1827-1908, 1866 (Box 56, Folder 2024)
  - Sparkes, Mrs. J.
    See: Edwards, Catherine Adelaide, box 22, folder 804
  - Spearman, Alexander Young, Sir, Bart., 1793-1874, 1871, undated (Box 56, Folder 2025)
  - Spencer, Frederick Spencer, Earl, 1798-1857, 1856 (Box 56, Folder 2026)
  - Spencer, John Poyntz Spencer, Earl, 1835-1910, 1894-1912, undated (Box 56, Folder 2027)
  - Spencer-Churchill, Henry John, Lord, 1797-1840, 1836 (Box 56, Folder 2028)
  - Spender, Edward Harold, 1864-1926, 1894 (Box 56, Folder 2029)
  - Spender, John A. (John Alfred), 1862- 1942, 1900-01 (Box 56, Folder 2030)
  - Stacpoole, Frederick, 1813-1907, 1890, undated (Box 56, Folder 2031)
  - Stamfordham, Arthur John Bigge, Baron, 1849-1931, 1890-1919, undated (Box 56, Folder 2032)
  - Stanesby, Joshua, fl. 1821-1854, 1851-52 (Box 56, Folder 2033)
  - Stanhope, Arthur Philip Stanhope, Earl, 1838-1905, 1868-95 (Box 56, Folder 2034)